I do not know.
I have not tried the engine too full.
The idea is not to be the fastest.
It should go and drive with it.
I should not be the fastest and operate around on a track.
It should hold and I drive hard it just breaks.
The plan is to drive without having to screw.
The hardest thing has been to make the gear control.
Wires that will steer the backdrop forwards that will match a 6 -switched box with back.
I think it's been the hardest on the whole car.
There are many holes in the body that air goes through.
Here air comes in through the hose that will cool down the turbo.
The warm air goes out through the grid at the back.
-Yeah, the warm air comes out here.
-Ferrari red learn the car to be?
Yes it is lacquered in Ferraris red.
-The weird would be otherwise.
Yes that's true.
Now the car is just lacquered.
When I had the car at the Elmia fair a few years ago.
I mounted it and pulled on color to see what it would look like.
Then the varnish would be for a few years so the car to move a bit.
Now you can grind it out and paint it as it should be with varnish and clear varnish.
I don't have that now.
Now it's just varnish.
In the coming year it will be sanded and varnished so that it will be perfect.
-When can you see this on the road?
Yes, it is partly inspected.
It is SRFO inspected but there is run and sound test left.
It is ready to be inspected now.
It should be done in 2 steps.